Guide to the Chinese Filmscript and Advertisement Collection, 1946-1985 RL.00223
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Advertisements and Film Description Series, 1953-1966 and undated, 1 boxes
  - 宣 传 资 料 Xuan Chuan Zi Liao, 1953-1966 and undated, 8 folders
    - 农村饮水卫生, 1965 (Box 1)
      Film Director: 江浩
    - 马蹄形回风灶, 1965 (Box 1)
    - 团结就是力量——第一届中日青年友好大联欢续集, 1966 January (Box 1)
    - 改造盐碱地, 1966 February (Box 1)
    - 电白的绿化, 1966 March (Box 1)
    - 茅棚飞出金凤凰, 1966 March (Box 1)
    - 秘密图纸, 1966 March 10 (Box 1)
      Film Director: 郝光
    - 奸细 (Box 1)
    - 南征北战 (Box 1)
    - 我们永远忠于党（纪录片） (Box 1)
    - 向海洋（故事片）, 1959 (Box 1)
    - 锡城的故事（故事片）, 1959 (Box 1)
    - 水上姊妹（故事片）, 1959 (Box 1)
    - 青春的脚步, 1957 (Box 1)
      Film Director: 严恭、苏里
    - 老兵新传, 1959 (Box 1)
    - 列兵邓志高（故事片）, 1958 (Box 1)
      Film Director: 雷铿
    - 柳堡的故事（故事片）, 1957 (Box 1)
      Film Director: 王苹、黄宗江
    - 两个巡逻兵（故事片）, 1958 (Box 1)
    - 狼牙山五壮士（故事片）, 1958 (Box 1)
      Film Director: 史文炽
    - 飞越天险（故事片）, 1959 (Box 1)
    - 党的女儿（故事片）, 1958 (Box 1)
      Film Director: 林农
    - 雪山泪, 1979 (Box 1)
      Film Director: 华纯、任鹏远
      Production Year: 1979
    - 阳光XX山南（纪录片） (Box 1)
    - 蓓蕾初开（戏曲艺术片）, 1960 (Box 1)
      Film Director: 阿妍
    - 雕龙记（彩色木偶片）, 1959 (Box 1)
      Film Director: 章超群、岳路、万超尘
    - 红色信号, 1959 (Box 1)
      Film Director: 虞哲光、陈正鸿
    - 三只蝴蝶, 1959 (Box 1)
    - 国防体育之歌 (Box 1)
      Film Director: 杨采
    - 不要乱开荒 (Box 1)
      Film Director: 王文彬
    - 为了和平（故事片）, 1956 (Box 1)
      Film Director: 黄佐临
    - 小林日记, 1965 (Box 1)
      Film Director: 胡进庆
    - 穆桂英大战洪州（彩色戏曲故事片）, 1963 (Box 1)
  - 宣 传 资 料 Miscellaneous, 2 folders
    - 山区女教师（越南） (Box 1)
      Film Director: 农益达
    - 秃鲁江畔之花（朝鲜）, 1964 (Box 1)
    - 金姬和银姬的命运（朝鲜）, 1974 (Box 1)
      Film Director: 朴学
      Production Year: 1974
    - 火车司机的儿子（朝鲜） (Box 1)
      Film Director: 朱东月
    - 爆炸（罗马尼亚） (Box 1)
      Film Director: 米尔恰·德勒甘
    - 第七届亚运会 (Box 1)
      Film Director: 中央新闻纪录电影制片厂
    - 回故乡之路（越南）, 1971 (Box 1)
      Film Director: 裴庭鹤
      Production Year: 1971
    - 一个护士的故事（朝鲜）, 1971 (Box 1)
      Film Director: 吴丙浩
    - 山姑娘（阿尔巴尼亚） (Box 1)
      Film Director: 季·阿纳格诺斯蒂
    - 永生的战士（朝鲜） (Box 1)
    - 车轮滚滚 (Box 1)
      Film Director: 今欣、尹一青
    - 创业, 1974 (Box 1)
    - 大浪淘沙, 1966 (Box 1)
      Production Year: 1966
    - 主课, 1976 (Box 1)
      Film Director: 广布道尔基
      Production Year: 1976
    - 渡江侦察记, 1974 (Box 1)
      Film Director: 汤化达、汤晓丹
    - 高山之鹰（朝鲜） (Box 1)
    - 斯特凡大公（罗马尼亚） (Box 1)
    - 海上明珠, 1976 (Box 1)
      Film Director: 林扬、王好为
    - 草原大寨镶黄旗 (Box 1)
    - 洪湖赤卫队, 1961 (Box 1)
      Film Director: 谢添、陈方千、徐枫
    - 征途, 1976 (Box 1)
      Film Director: 颜碧丽、包起成
    - 开山的人, 1976 (Box 1)
      Film Director: 魏荣
    - 阿夏河的秘密, 1976 (Box 1)
      Film Director: 颜碧丽、沈浮、武珍年
    - 南征北站, 1974 (Box 1)
      Film Director: 成荫、王炎
    - 南海风云, 1976 (Box 1)
      Film Director: 景慕逵、张勇手
    - 百花争艳, 1976 (Box 1)
      Film Director: 傅杰
    - 小将, 1975 (Box 1)
      Film Director: 中叔皇
      Production Year: 1975
    - 难忘的战斗, 1976 (Box 1)
      Film Director: 汤晓丹、天然、于本正
    - 艳阳天, 1973 (Box 1)
      Production Year: 1973
    - 园丁之歌, 1974 (Box 1)
      Film Director: 沙丹、郑国权
    - 伟大的领袖和导师毛泽东主席纪念堂奠基仪式 (Box 1)
    - 长在屋里的竹笋, 1976 (Box 1)
      Film Director: 胡进清、周克勤
    - 树苗, 1976 (Box 1)
      Film Director: 方润南
    - 多瑙河三角洲的警报（罗马尼亚） (Box 1)
    - 大潮汛之夜, 1974 (Box 1)
      Film Director: 唐澄、邬强
    - 马王堆二、三号汉墓发掘记 (Box 1)
    - 非洲之角, 1961 (Box 1)
    - 访几内亚 (Box 1)
    - 成昆铁路 (Box 1)
    - 带响的弓箭, 1974 (Box 1)
    - 庆祝五一 (Box 1)
    - 时刻准备上战场——中国人民解放军第三届体育运动会 (Box 1)
    - 人老心红, 1975 (Box 1)
    - 拣煤渣, 1975 (Box 1)
      Film Director: 武珍年
    - 杂技英豪 (Box 1)
    - 国庆颂 (Box 1)
    - 户县农民画 (Box 1)
    - 黄河万里行 (Box 1)
    - 中缅友谊开新花——邓颖超副委员长访问缅甸 (Box 1)
    - 热烈欢庆《毛泽东选集》第五卷出版发行 (Box 1)
    - 千万不要忘记 (Box 1)
      Film Director: 刘璐
    - 广西桂剧团 (Box 1)
    - 齐齐哈尔市马戏团 (Box 1)
    - 节振国 (Box 1)
      Film Director: 于彦夫、曾未之
    - 雷雨之前, 1975 (Box 1)
      Film Director: 李文虎
    - 红军不怕远征难, 1976 (Box 1)
      Film Director: 王苹、黄宝善
    - 小店春早, 1976 (Box 1)
      Film Director: 邓一民、徐纪宏
    - 审椅子, 1976 (Box 1)
      Film Director: 梁廷铎
    - 沂蒙颂, 1975 (Box 1)
      Film Director: 李文虎、景幕逵
    - 账目与钥匙 (Box 1)
      Film Director: 吕振民
  - 银 屏 花 絮 Yin Ping Hua Xu, No.3, 7-10, and 60, 1 folder (Box 1)
  - 电 影 介 绍 Dian Ying Jie Shao, No. 7706-7707, 7801-7923, 7901,and 7908-7909, 1 folder (Box 1)
- Documentary and Newsreel Scripts Series, 1946(?)-1985 and undated, 3 boxes
  Transcripts and shot lists for newsreels and documentary films. These focus on specific subjects, events or personal stories. Scripts in boxes 2 and 3 are arranged by subject, then chronologically within each subject. The date on the earliest item in box 3 is questionable. There are also a few special issues. For example, a special issue in February 1966 is entitled: Chairman Mao's Good Student- Jiao Yulu. Scripts for Xin Wen Jian Bao in box 4 are arranged by number and year.
  - 政 沸 Politics; 1958-1978 and undated, 7 folders
    - 纪念列宁诞辰九十周年, 1959 (Box 2)
      Film Director: 李堃
    - 庆祝捷克斯洛伐克解放十五周年, 1959 (Box 2)
    - 百万农奴站起来, 1959 (Box 2)
    - 支援南朝鲜人民爱国正义斗争, 1960 (Box 2)
    - 全民欢腾庆五一, 1960 (Box 2)
    - 领袖和我们同劳动, 1958 (Box 2)
    - 兄弟的友谊, 1961 (Box 2)
    - 古巴必胜, 1961 (Box 2)
    - 欢庆五一, 1961 (Box 2)
    - 两种命运的决战, 1961 (Box 2)
    - 非洲之角, 1961 (Box 2)
    - 不要忘记这个地方, 1964 (Box 2)
    - 刚果（利）人民必胜, 1964 (Box 2)
    - 越南南方中部人民的斗争, 1965 (Box 2)
    - 庆祝古巴解放六周年, 1965 (Box 2)
    - 美帝国主义从多米尼亚滚出去, 1965 (Box 2)
    - 高举胡伯伯奖旗前进, 1965 (Box 2)
      Film Director: 八一电影制片厂译制
    - 庆祝越南南方民族解放阵线成立五周年, 1965 (Box 2)
    - 翻身农奴见太阳, 1966 (Box 2)
    - 美国人民的觉醒, 1966 (Box 2)
    - 阿尔巴尼亚在革命化大道上, 1966 (Box 2)
    - 坚决支持阿拉伯人民反侵略斗争, 1967 (Box 2)
      Production Year: 1967
    - 抗议缅甸奈温反动政府反华暴行, 1967 (Box 2)
    - 莫三鼻给人民在战斗中前进, 1972 (Box 2)
      Production Year: 1972
    - 庆祝五一, 1973 (Box 2)
    - 宝塔山下不老松, 1973 (Box 2)
    - 广阔天地育新人, 1974 (Box 2)
    - 批林批孔特辑, 1974 (Box 2)
    - 特赦释放全部在押战争罪犯, 1975 (Box 2)
    - 庆祝西藏自治区成立十周年, 1976 (Box 2)
    - 紧跟华主席狠批四人帮, 1977 (Box 2)
      Production Year: 1977
    - 周恩来同志少年时期在沈阳, 1978 (Box 2)
      Film Director: 沈阳市电化教育馆
      Production Year: 1978
    - 毛泽东主席纪念堂, 1978 (Box 2)
    - 越南当局驱赶华侨纪实, 1978 (Box 2)
    - 毛主席视察人民公社, 1978 (Box 2)
    - 祖国处处是家乡 (Box 2)
      Film Director: 八一电影制片厂
    - 一代新人在成长 (Box 2)
      Film Director: 珠江电影制片厂
    - 我们在毛主席身边唱歌 (Box 2)
      Film Director: 北京电影制片厂
    - 亚洲风暴 (Box 2)
  - 外 交 Foreign Relations; 1961-1977 and undated, 6 folders
    - 友谊常青, 1961 (Box 2)
    - 中国代表团访问古巴, 1961 (Box 2)
    - 扩大的日内瓦会议, 1961 (Box 2)
    - 老挝见闻, 1961 (Box 2)
    - 喜迎"胞波"度佳节, 1961 (Box 2)
    - 中国经济建设展览会在马里, 1964 (Box 2)
    - 记者贝却敌访问越南南方, 1965 (Box 2)
      Film Director: 中央新闻纪录电影制片厂译制
    - 陈毅副总理访问阿富汗、巴基斯坦、尼泊尔, 1965 (Box 2)
    - 周总理访问巴基斯坦, 1965 (Box 2)
    - 热烈欢迎阿尔巴尼亚党政代表团, 1966 (Box 2)
    - 热烈欢迎秘鲁贵宾, 1972 (Box 2)
    - 毛泽东主席会见基辛格博士, 1973 (Box 2)
    - 毛泽东主席会见马里国家元首特拉奥雷, 1973 (Box 2)
    - 热烈欢迎许锬外长访华, 1973 (Box 2)
    - 毛泽东主席会见埃切维利亚总统, 1973 (Box 2)
    - 毛泽东主席会见蓬皮杜总统, 1973 (Box 2)
    - 坦赞铁路在建设中, 1973 (Box 2)
    - 毛泽东主席会见特鲁多总统, 1973 (Box 2)
    - 毛泽东主席会见惠特拉姆总统, 1973 (Box 2)
    - 毛泽东会见尼泊尔国王和王后, 1973 (Box 2)
    - 毛泽东主席会见马卡里奥斯总统等贵宾, 1974 (Box 2)
    - 毛泽东主席会见桑戈尔总统等贵宾, 1974 (Box 2)
    - 毛泽东主席会见马科斯总统夫人, 1974 (Box 2)
    - 毛泽东主席会见戈翁将军等贵宾, 1974 (Box 2)
    - 毛泽东主席会见莱奥·延德曼斯首相, 1975 (Box 2)
    - 毛泽东主席会见金日成主席, 1975 (Box 2)
    - 毛泽东主席会见贾瓦拉总统等贵宾, 1975 (Box 2)
    - 热烈欢迎努伊拉总理, 1975 (Box 2)
    - 毛泽东主席会见马里国家元首特拉奥雷的夫人, 1975 (Box 2)
    - 热烈欢迎泰国贵宾, 1975 (Box 2)
    - 中国共产党代表团访问朝鲜, 1976 (Box 2)
    - 热烈欢迎莫桑比克战友, 1976 (Box 2)
    - 热烈欢迎达科斯塔总统, 1976 (Box 2)
    - 欢迎您华主席派来的亲人, 1977 (Box 2)
    - 在英雄的国土上——陈永贵同志访问民主柬埔寨, 1977 (Box 2)
    - 毛泽东主席会见布托总统等贵宾 (Box 2)
    - 毛泽东主席会见布迈丁主席 (Box 2)
    - 热烈欢迎喀麦隆贵宾 (Box 2)
    - 热烈欢迎赞比亚友好代表团 (Box 2)
    - 西哈努克亲王访问广州 (Box 2)
  - 军 事 Military; 1964-1966, 1976-1984 and undated, 4 folders
    - 自投罗网, 1964 (Box 2)
    - 草原铁骑, 1964 (Box 2)
    - 战地炊烟, 1964 (Box 2)
    - 文艺新兵, 1965 (Box 2)
    - 好八连野营归来, 1965 (Box 2)
    - 江河湖海练硬功, 1965 (Box 2)
    - 尖刀八连, 1965 (Box 2)
    - 勤俭起家的修理连, 1965 (Box 2)
    - 英雄海军再获大捷, 1965 (Box 2)
    - 钢铁战士麦贤得, 1966 (Box 2)
    - 鹅高战斗, 1966 (Box 2)
    - 鸟鸣森林伏击战, 1966 (Box 2)
    - 军民联防模范连, 1966 (Box 2)
    - 海上文化工作队, 1966 (Box 2)
    - 常备不懈的南宁民兵, 1966 (Box 2)
    - 一心为公的硬骨头战士张春玉, 1966 (Box 2)
    - 雪原民兵, 1966 (Box 2)
    - 井冈山, 1976 (Box 2)
      Film Director: 上海电影制片厂
    - 今日洪湖赤卫队, 1977 (Box 2)
    - 井冈红旗, 1977 (Box 2)
    - 长空利剑, 1979 (Box 2)
    - 黄埔校友喜相逢, 1984 (Box 2)
      Production Year: 1984
    - 战斗歌声传友情 (Box 2)
    - 敌来必打 每打必胜 (Box 2)
    - 在保卫祖国的岗位上 (Box 2)
    - 做雷锋式的战斗——沈阳部队学雷锋简报 (Box 2)
    - 东帅烈火 (Box 2)
    - 海上练兵 (Box 2)
  - 工 业 Industry, 1959-1978 and undated, 6 folders
    - 上海英雄交响曲, 1959 (Box 3)
      Film Director: 上海天马电影制片厂
    - 第26号简报台本, 1960 (Box 3)
    - 白手起家闹革新, 1960 (Box 3)
      Film Director: 王映东、白国柱
    - 革新花开遍地红（一）装卸机械化, 1960 (Box 3)
    - 革新花开遍地红（二）包装工人闹革新, 1960 (Box 3)
      Film Director: 高仲朋
    - 革新花开遍地红（三）苦干巧干的红旗厂, 1960 (Box 3)
    - 革新花开遍地红（四）一步登天, 1960 (Box 3)
      Film Director: 白国柱、王映东
    - 革新花开遍地红（五）更上一层楼, 1960 (Box 3)
      Film Director: 吴本立、王映东
    - 技术革命之花, 1960 (Box 3)
    - 小高炉大闹革新, 1960 (Box 3)
      Film Director: 刘文渺
    - 夺煤先锋, 1961 (Box 3)
    - 红旗机车, 1961 (Box 3)
    - 毛泽东号, 1965 (Box 3)
      Film Director: 铁道部展览处
    - 全国先进工具展览会, 1965 (Box 3)
    - 矿山工人闹革新, 1965 (Box 3)
    - 废品不废, 1966 (Box 3)
    - 马钢工人赶大庆, 1966 (Box 3)
    - 茅棚飞出金凤凰, 1966 (Box 3)
    - 革旧创新的工厂, 1966 (Box 3)
    - 勤俭节约的修理厂, 1966 (Box 3)
    - 我们都是普通的劳动者, 1966 (Box 3)
    - 寸木必争, 1966 (Box 3)
    - 祖国大地气象新, 1972 (Box 3)
    - 船台战歌, 1972 (Box 3)
    - 南京长江大桥——施工技术, 1973 (Box 3)
      Film Director: 上海科学教育电影制片厂
    - 人民邮政, 1974 (Box 3)
    - 沸腾的开滦, 1974 (Box 3)
    - 战金山——前进中的上海石油化工总厂, 1975 (Box 3)
    - 林海战旗红, 1976 (Box 3)
    - 电气化铁路, 1977 (Box 3)
      Film Director: 峨嵋电影制片厂
    - 土法造炸药, 1978 (Box 3)
      Film Director: 北京科学教育电影制片厂
    - 中国邮票, 1978 (Box 3)
    - 一个女工的自述 (Box 3)
    - 勇攀高峰的深井钻井队 (Box 3)
    - 襄渝铁路 (Box 3)
    - 从一件小事说起 (Box 3)
    - 亦工亦农 (Box 3)
    - 敢想敢干的大庆人 (Box 3)
  - 农 业 Agriculture, 1960-1978, 7 folders
    - 农村简报第三号, 1960 (Box 3)
    - 农村简报第六号, 1960 (Box 3)
    - 农村简报第七号, 1960 (Box 3)
    - 各行各业支援农业, 1960 (Box 3)
      Film Director: 陈健
    - 把青春献给农业, 1960 (Box 3)
    - 发扬南泥湾精神, 1961 (Box 3)
    - 黄河巨变, 1961 (Box 3)
    - 大寨之路, 1964 (Box 3)
    - 东北农业在前进, 1965 (Box 3)
      Film Director: 长春电影制片厂
    - 与海争田, 1965 (Box 3)
    - 大地春光, 1965 (Box 3)
    - 莆田山区赶大寨, 1965 (Box 3)
    - 贫农下中农的喜事, 1965 (Box 3)
    - 北京农业的大跃进, 1965 (Box 3)
    - 千方百计争丰收, 1965 (Box 3)
    - 亦工亦农经营生猪, 1965 (Box 3)
    - 旦寨大队战干旱, 1966 (Box 3)
    - 杨谈人谈抗灾夺丰收, 1966 (Box 3)
    - 冰天雪地修水利, 1966 (Box 3)
    - 全国学大寨 大寨怎么办, 1966 (Box 3)
    - 石屋大队, 1966 (Box 3)
    - 欢呼夏粮大丰收, 1967 (Box 3)
    - 丰收喜讯, 1971 (Box 3)
    - 战海河, 1972 (Box 3)
    - 祖国大地气象新, 1972 (Box 3)
    - 征服黄河的战斗, 1972 (Box 3)
    - 韶山银河, 1973 (Box 3)
    - 搬山填沟造平原, 1973 (Box 3)
    - 林茂粮丰气象新, 1973 (Box 3)
    - 金稻银花齐跃进, 1973 (Box 3)
    - 喜看农业大丰收（一）, 1973 (Box 3)
    - 喜看农业大丰收（三）, 1973 (Box 3)
    - 昔阳农业新气象, 1974 (Box 3)
    - 大寨花开万里香, 1975 (Box 3)
    - 为普及大寨县而奋斗 特辑（一）, 1975 (Box 3)
    - 普及大寨县——全国农业学大寨会议, 1975 (Box 3)
      Film Director: 农业电影制片厂
    - 为普及大寨县而奋斗 特辑（二）, 1975 (Box 3)
    - 种子标准化, 1977 (Box 3)
      Film Director: 湖北新闻纪录电影制片厂
    - 虎头山上访亲人, 1977 (Box 3)
    - 反渗透淡化苦咸水, 1978 (Box 3)
      Film Director: 西安电影制片厂
    - 地下寻水计, 1978 (Box 3)
    - 访毛田, 1978 (Box 3)
    - 祖国新貌, 1978 (Box 3)
    - 为农服务为农忙 (Box 3)
    - 人定胜天 (Box 3)
      Film Director: 徐肖冰、沈容、肖树琴、陈纯烈
  - 文 化 Culture, 1960-1985 and undated, 2 folders
    - 中国杂技团访问苏丹, 1960 (Box 3)
    - 清明时节, 1961 (Box 3)
    - 在英雄的国土上——中国电影学习团访越纪事, 1973 (Box 3)
    - 我们的心是连在一起的——阿尔巴尼亚歌剧院芭蕾舞剧团访华, 1972 (Box 3)
    - 日本齿轮座剧团在北京, 1972 (Box 3)
    - 杂技（2）, 1973 (Box 3)
    - 杂技（3）, 1973 (Box 3)
    - 杂技（6）, 1973 (Box 3)
    - 中国广州杂技团访问澳大利亚, 1975 (Box 3)
    - 驯兽, 1977 (Box 3)
    - 圆明园, 1980 (Box 3)
      Production Year: 1980
    - 黄鹤归来——愉快的旅行, 1985 (Box 3)
      Production Year: 1985
    - 美国西部七奇 (Box 3)
      Film Director: 上海电影译制厂译制
  - 教 育 Education, 1946(?)-1976, 1 folder
    - 天天向上, 1946 (Box 3)
      Production Year: 1946?
    - 黑山北关小学教学改革——献给全国文教群英会, 1960 (Box 3)
      Film Director: 何钟辛
    - 祁连山下一大学, 1960 (Box 3)
    - 半工半读育新人, 1965 (Box 3)
    - 江西共产主义劳动大学, 1965 (Box 3)
    - 花儿朵朵向阳开（1）, 1973 (Box 3)
    - 花儿朵朵向阳开（2）, 1973 (Box 3)
    - 花儿朵朵向阳开（3）, 1973 (Box 3)
    - 复旦校园卷狂飙, 1976 (Box 3)
  - 体 育 Sports, 1960 -1975 and undated, 1 folder
    - 全国公安消防体育运动会台本, 1960 (Box 3)
    - 第26届世界乒乓球锦标赛（上集）, 1961 (Box 3)
    - 1965年北京国际乒乓球邀请赛 (Box 3)
    - 一九七二年全国田径运动会, 1972 (Box 3)
    - 山乡小体操, 1974 (Box 3)
    - 南粤体坛开新花, 1975 (Box 3)
    - 碧波传友谊, 1975 (Box 3)
  - 卫 生, 医 疗 和 科 学 Health, Medicine, and Science, 1960-1977, 1 folder
    - 卫生红旗, 1960 (Box 3)
    - 北京医疗队在阿里, 1977 (Box 3)
    - 冰雪南极, 1969 (Box 3)
      Production Year: 1969
  - 新 闻 简 报 Xin Wen Jian Bao, No.1-19; No.29-41; 1965-1969; and 1971-1977, 15 folders (Box 4)
- Feature Filmscripts Series, undated, 1 boxes
  Filmscripts for 12 Chinese and foreign feature films.
  - 外 国 电 影 Foreign Films, B-K, L-S, Y-Z, 3 folders
    - 百合花（苏联）, 1958 (Box 5)
    - 大使们（突尼斯） (Box 5)
      Film Director: 纳赛尔·克塔里
    - 当十一月来临的时候（阿尔巴尼亚） (Box 5)
    - 好事不成双（苏联） (Box 5)
      Film Director: 阿·加布里也良
    - 看不见的战线（朝鲜） (Box 5)
    - 老枪（法国） (Box 5)
      Film Director: 罗·昂里科
    - 卖花姑娘（朝鲜） (Box 5)
    - 三滴血, 1960 (Box 5)
      Film Director: 孙敬、郭阳庭
    - 樱, 1979 (Box 5)
      Film Director: 詹相持、韩小磊
    - 沼泽地里的阳光（土耳其） (Box 5)
  - 中 国 电 影 Chinese Films, B-D, F-L, Q-S, W-Z, and Miscellaneous, 9 folders
    - 春苗, 1975 (Box 5)
      Film Director: 谢晋、颜碧丽、梁廷铎
    - 白毛女, 1972 (Box 5)
    - 大刀记, 1977 (Box 5)
      Film Director: 汤化达、王秀文
    - 地道战, 1965 (Box 5)
      Film Director: 任旭东
    - 杜十娘, 1957 (Box 5)
    - 风雪配, 1982 (Box 5)
      Film Director: 吴培民
      Production Year: 1982
    - 黑三角, 1977 (Box 5)
      Film Director: 刘春霖、陈方千
    - 红灯记, 1970 (Box 5)
      Production Year: 1970
    - 红军桥, 1964 (Box 5)
      Film Director: 钱运达
    - 今夜星光灿烂, 1980 (Box 5)
    - 苦菜花, 1965 (Box 5)
    - 金玉姬, 1959 (Box 5)
    - 雷锋, 1964 (Box 5)
      Film Director: 董兆琪
    - 李慧娘, 1981 (Box 5)
      Film Director: 邓逸民、沙洁、刘琼
      Production Year: 1981
    - 燎原, 1962 (Box 5)
      Film Director: 张骏祥、顾而已
    - 青松岭, 1965 (Box 5)
    - 三毛流浪记——相依为命, 1984 (Box 5)
      Film Director: 阿达、朱康林
    - 闪闪的红星, 1974 (Box 5)
      Film Director: 李俊、李昴
    - 送粮, 1966 (Box 5)
      Film Director: 林岚
    - 万吨水压机战歌, 1972 (Box 5)
      Film Director: 胡进庆、邬强
    - 五彩路, 1960 (Box 5)
    - 小螺号, 1975 (Box 5)
      Film Director: 刘欣
    - 新队员, 1960 (Box 5)
      Film Director: 周伟
    - 艳阳天, 1973 (Box 5)
    - 一声惊雷, 1978 (Box 5)
      Film Director: 苏乐慈
    - 游乡, 1965 (Box 5)
    - 张飞审瓜, 1980 (Box 5)
      Film Director: 钱运达 葛桂云
    - 安徽戏曲集锦, 1959 (Box 5)
      Film Director: 郭筠
    - 戏曲集锦片, 1965 (Box 5)
- Newspaper Clipping Scrapbook Series, 1950-1959 and undated, 1 boxes
  Scrapbook containing film reviews (many on foreign films), publicity material, articles on film production and distribution, and reports on film conferences, festivals, and award ceremonies.
  - 报 刊 剪 辑 Newspaper clips, 1 scrapbook of clips (Box 6)
- Microfilm Master Reels, 1 box
  8 silver duplicate microfilm reels of the collection.
  - Microfilm reels (8 reels) (Box 7)